Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Yes, my magic allows me to manipulate blood as I please.
Ever since I cast that healing spell on you, I've maintained total control over your blood as well.
And now for your first order.
I want you to kill every one of these weaklings with your own hands.
Do a perfect job and leave no one alive.
Under the control of the Queen of Witches, Asta tried to kill his friends.
Stop this! I'll make you a deal!
No. No matter where you run, your ties to me cannot be broken.
You are my daughter, after all. And family lasts forever.
What do you mean by that?
You're not my family. And you never were.
Cause the Black Bulls are my family!
Fools are my family!
Vanessa's fervent pleas on behalf of her companions awakened a new power.
At last, the Red Thread of Fate.
It dispelled Puppet's blood?
I can already tell. It'll always side with me and those I hold dear.
Which means you and I don't have any ties.
Please be with us.
.
履き潰した靴のレッシュアート 出発で一体どこだっけな
いつかのページとひらぐった 言い訳ばかり探している
毎日にさよなら告げるよ 走り出す列車に飛び乗った
小さくては見えないけど 大丈夫さ そんな気がするんだ
Your Majesty! Look! I made a doll out of my thread!
Oh my! You've done a lovely job!
I want to use my magic power to make other people happy!
Well, how sweet! I'm sure you will, Vanessa!
Somewhere along the way in my quest for absolute perfection,
It seems that I lost sight of an extremely precious truth.
When one is imperfect, there is a certain kind of power that can be gathered from one's emotions.
She could never have learned that spell during her time with me.
But now that she is free to be her imperfect self, she's become perfect.
Do as you see fit. It seems I must admit defeat.
Blood recovery magic.
Curse-breaking blood-filled cocoon.
Hey, I'm all healed up.
What just happened?
It must have taken a lot of magic to do that.
The Queen really is powerful, huh?
Did we... win?
You were so amazing, Vanessa!
You did it! Your new spell saved all of us!
I'm so relieved!
Oh, Sel! So am I! You had me worried sick!
I don't know what I'd do if I had lost you!
Hey, everything's okay!
Except that you're half-naked again.
Oh, wow! Guess so!
Long time no see, you two!
Yeah, it's been a while.
Nice work, you little tiger!
All of this is thanks to you.
No, it isn't.
It was everyone here.
My friends are the reason I could use that spell.
Thank you all.
Guess you're right.
Hey, wait. I think... yeah.
The pain's like 100% gone!
My body feels even better than it did before this whole thing started!
That's our Asta.
Knock him down and he just gets right back up.
And in case you haven't noticed, you need to put a shirt on!
Crap, you're right!
Who does that remind you of?
I don't know.
Come on, Noelle! This is cool!
Now that I'm back to normal, my muscles are way bigger and stronger!
This bird...
I'm so happy all those bad guys are gone now!
They're gonna be in big trouble if they come back!
Apparently, the Eye of the Midnight Sun came here looking for a magic stone.
Do you know where it might be?
The magic stone you speak of is most likely this. However, it's of no use to me. You may take it.
Are you serious? Thank you so much, Your Majesty! Wow!
No way! I was not expecting it to be that easy! Yami's gonna be thrilled with us when we get back!
Okay, so we know this is what the Eye of the Midnight Sun was after, but do you know why they would want it?
Who are those guys and what are they trying to do? Got any info?
That stone is a type of magic item that enhances the power of the individual who wears it.
But only a member of the Elf Tribe is able to use it effectively.
Huh? Elf Tribe?
They're quite gifted in magic. Many centuries ago, their kind resided in the place that is now known as the Forsaken Realm.
Every member of the Elf Tribe was blessed with unbelievable magical prowess. Some even had capabilities that rivaled my own strength.
She was alive then? So she's hundreds of years old? She really takes care of her skin!
Sadly, they fell into war with the humans who outnumbered them, and the Elves were annihilated.
The third eye that appeared on Fauna's head before she came to her senses is a kind of forbidden magic.
However, Fauna was not the one who unleashed its power. She was merely a vessel controlled by another entity.
Forbidden magic is beyond the reach of humans, you see.
Okay, now you've lost me.
The casting of a forbidden spell requires extraordinary mana, as well as some sort of sacrifice.
For example, the ancient demon was summoned with the highest rank of forbidden magic by the leader of the Elves.
Do you mean that demon?
This Midnight Sun is a curious lot. I wonder if they might be descended from the Elf Tribe.
Hold on. This is the clan of evil monsters in this storybook my grandmother read to me.
Does this mean they were the Elves all along?
All this important information is coming at us so fast, I can't keep up!
If I don't take notes, I feel like I might forget everything!
Listen well, Asta. The two weapons you carry are all that remain of the pair of magic swords once wielded by the leader of the Elf Tribe.
I don't get it!
Yikes! Looks like trying to follow that story made Asta's head explode!
Get it together, birdbrain!
His feeble mind can't handle much more of this!
Should you continue to fight against the Midnight Sun, you may soon discover who they are.
He doesn't short-circuit first!
So, I guess you guys are going to head back to the Diamond Kingdom now.
That's right. The Queen of Witches used her puppet's blood ability to create this special medicine for us.
If I give it to the King disguised as a longevity potion, I should be able to thwart Morris' ambition.
That way, I can reform the Diamond Kingdom into a peaceful nation.
And I'll support Marzy Boy in pulling off this master plan of his. The only thing I've ever really cared about is making it to the top, and this seems like it's the fastest way to get there, right?
Uh, are we sure about this guy?
I'll try and become worthy of your approval. And then, I'll come back and see you, Teach.
We'll look out for Fauna while you're gone. Be careful and try not to work too hard, okay, you guys?
If you need us, we're here for you. I'll make sure he's not naked around her, or I'll try at least.
Fauna, please. Will you wait for me? I'm going to set everything right. Someday, the Diamond Kingdom will be a place that you can come home to.
I'll wait for you as long as I have to. And once Diamond is finally at peace, you and I will see the whole world together.
Asta, I was glad when you said that I was your friend. If you're ever in trouble, I promise you, I'll be right there to help you out of it again, no matter what.
No matter what. That's what friends are for, right?
Yeah! And the same goes for me, too. Just say the word, and I'll bust into the Diamond Kingdom and save you!
You are free, my child. But seeing as this is still your home, I would like you to come back and visit any time your heart desires.
If you start off in second place, then the top will be there right in front of your nose.
You'd better focus on helping Mars instead of just surpassing him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I know. I know.
This guy's a lost cause.
Sorry I'm late!
Oh, hey, Vanessa.
Are you guys all done with your goodbyes? Not to rush, but I'd kind of like to get out of this creepy forest.
Oh, rats. This place is crawling with girls and I didn't get a single date.
Hey, what are you laughing at? Quit it!
Thank you for healing, Asta. I hope you and I meet again someday.
It's not that big of a deal.
Oh, glad you made it back. Where'd your shirt go?
You're so chill! What gives?
Anyway, guess what? We found a magic stone! How cool is that?
What? Listen, Asta. Now that you're patched up, your first mission is getting us more supplies.
Sorry, yes sir! I'll grab everything we need and be back here in a flash!
Wait a second. Don't tell me the rest of the team is still out there.
What, you think someone's dead in a ditch or something?
Maybe.
Well, unless you want to die too, I suggest you hurry up and get shopping already.
I'm on my way!
Captain?
Yeah, yeah. Welcome back.
Thanks a lot.
Hey, look what I bought!
That quick? Creepy.
Okay, boss. What's my next mission?
Uh, rest up. You work too much. No more missions for a while.
And put a damn shirt on.
Oh, come on. If you take away my missions, what do I have to wear?
Your muscles.
There, there. Don't you think you're overreacting?
Hey, when you're done being dramatic, I brought some clothes for you to wear.
We're home!
Look at that. They're still alive.
That was definitely Magna's voice.
Oh, right. He and Luck went into a dungeon looking for a way to fix my arms. I owe those guys a huge thank you.
That must have been a heck of a trip!
Our angel had lost his wings. And so we went adventuring. A risky thing.
Wandering in the darkness, drowning in the loneliness, the breaking of my heart seemed endless.
Then a vision of you came into view.
Feeling you near, I let go of my fear and found the courage to push on through.
This is way out of character!
The mana is calling.
Not you too!
As the journey grew longer, my body grew stronger.
And on through the dungeon we'd go, knocking down each and every foe.
Yet there was one secret which we did not know.
How could we hope to salvage your arms that had suffered such harm?
By crushing regret, we were soon overcome, and that's when we knew we had to go home.
The mana is calling me!
But my arms are all better now, you guys!
Well, that's great news, you jerk! Why didn't you tell us?
Yeah, thanks anyway.
Hey, good for you, Asta! Why don't we spar a bit?
I'm good!
We're back.
It's Ghosh! Oh, I forgot, he and Gordon took a trip to the Royal Library to research a cure for my arms.
I'd better thank them too.
How they turned into a couple of nerds!
My eyes have opened at last to the splendor of magic.
Every spell is a grand work of art.
Wouldn't you agree with me, Professor Gordon?
What is happening to these people?!
I still can't hear anything this guy says.
But as the key to restoring Asta's arms has yet to be discovered,
we simply must manufacture some sort of curse-canceling spell no matter how long it takes.
Just you wait, Asta, we can make you whole again.
Don't worry about it, I'm all good now!
What is wrong with you?! I told you that I would take care of it!
Go get cursed again right now or else, you selfish little-
Hey, are you okay there? Your nose is bleeding!
That's because you made me angry!
It's still going!
It's fine! Just shut up!
Ah, I know.
It's when you focus your thoughts and energy on the happiness of someone who stared here.
I realized this after spending so much time with you alone in a library.
I think I might have just found the solution to our problem.
No, that's not going to work.
If that was right, you would be a sister, of course.
You'd have secrets to be treated with Asta as well.
Ridiculous. I need to look at Marie for a moment.
Asta is as dear to you as your sister.
Am I your sister, Asta's family team, which means Asta's friend,
a term which refers to me in case that is clear, is also family.
Yes, I understand.
Wait, is that Sharma?
Oh, baby mushrooms!
Guess what, guys?
I got infected with magic mushroom paris!
Are you still eating?!
Don't look at me!
I can't transform now! This is so embarrassing!
How is that embarrassing?
Sharmy, you gotta stop eating those nasty things!
I can't.
Every time you eat one, three more pop up!
One, one, there's plenty.
Hard pass!
Look! We picked up all kinds of delicious goodies for everyone in my shot!
So you risked your life for some gross food?
Yeah, but we didn't find a way to fix your arms.
Sorry about that.
What a surprise.
Wait, what? Your bandages are gone!
Does this mean you've already been healed?
How did that happen? Oh, I'm so embarrassed!
Is there anything that doesn't embarrass you?
You know, now that we've got plenty of stuff to eat and drink,
and I've taken that workaholic muscle head off duty for a while,
I say we ought to use this opportunity to do it up big.
I'm saying we party!
All right!
I'm so happy I can eat with my arms again!
Oh, I just realized no one was around this morning,
so those guys never got fed.
You, get on it!
On what?
Hey there, what's up?
You must be hungry!
Not again!
Oh yeah, there's laundry to do, too.
Where am I supposed to hang all this stuff up?
Hey, the cleaning hasn't been done yet, either.
Hey, kid!
Yes, sir!
Who told you you could open the door, numbskull?
Now go get me some toilet paper!
Sorry!
Okay, what's next?
Captain Yami may have ordered him to rest up,
but that hasn't slowed Asta down for a second.
Yeah, what he lacks in brains, he makes up for in energy.
It's true.
This is the place for me.
What did I gain by joining the outside world?
A family to call my own.
Wow, I will not have the purpose to have the music outside.
I'll make it true
My song, my days
This world, I'll make it true
I'll make it true
La la la,諦めない
My song, my days
音符を書き加えてく
流れくなった道さのくらには
輝ける明日を映すメロディー
Clover Kicks!
How come?
What's bothering you?
So if that salamander thing was surrounded by flames,
how come Fauna didn't get burned to a crisp?
Uh, because it's magic?
Okay, and when we use Sea Dragon's lair to go underwater,
how come our clothes never get wet?
Again, it's magic.
And if kelp grows underwater,
then how come it doesn't turn the ocean into broth?
Leave all of the culinary questions to the brilliant Professor Charmy.
You see, the explanation is quite elementary.
Kelp possesses a component within its cells known as glutamic acid.
That's the stuff that produces a broth.
Because of a characteristic we call selective permeability,
kelp is able to take in only the materials necessary to survive
and excrete everything that's extraneous.
And since the broth-producing glutamic acid helps to keep the kelp alive,
it remains inside the cells until the organism eventually dries up and dies.
When that happens,
it's cell-bursts open, releasing the glutamic acid,
and creating the broth!
Just say it's magic and leave it at that.
I'm sure the Eye of the Midnight Sun
is still trying to get their hands on the magic stones,
but I wonder what they really hope to accomplish.
Black Clover, page 66.
The Secret of the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
My magic is drinking like a fish.